<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist>
  <schema id="org.gnome.shell.extensions.Picture-desktop-multiple-widget" path="/org/gnome/shell/extensions/Picture-desktop-multiple-widget/">
    
    <key name="widgets-config" type="s">
      <default>'[{"id": "widget-default", "widget-size": 200, "widget-aspect-ratio": 1.0, "widget-position-x": 100, "widget-position-y": 100, "image-path": "", "widget-timeout": 60, "widget-corner-radius": 20, "time-last-update": 0, "current-image-path": ""}]'</default>
      <summary>List of configurations for multiple image widgets (JSON array)</summary>
      <description>
        A JSON string containing an array of objects. Each object represents a single desktop image widget and contains the following properties:
        
        - id (string): Unique identifier for the widget.
        - widget-size (int): Size of the image widget in pixels. Controls the width and height of the desktop image widget.
        - widget-aspect-ratio (double): Aspect ratio of the image widget. Defines the aspect ratio (width to height) of the desktop image widget.
        - widget-position-x (int): X position of the image widget. Sets the horizontal position of the desktop image widget.
        - widget-position-y (int): Y position of the image widget. Sets the vertical position of the desktop image widget.
        - image-path (string): Path to the image file or folder. Specifies the file path of the image to be displayed on the desktop.
        - widget-timeout (int): Timeout for image updates. Defines the interval in seconds for updating the image displayed on the desktop.
        - widget-corner-radius (int): Corner radius of the image widget. Sets the corner radius for the desktop image widget, giving it rounded corners.
        - time-last-update (int): Time of last update of the image.
        - current-image-path (string): Path to the currently displayed image. Stores the path of the image currently being displayed on the desktop.
      </description>
    </key>

  </schema>
</schemalist>